mb.com.ph 2018-10-18

# Privacy Policy » Manila Bulletin

### Privacy Policy

_**Your privacy is important to us.**_

By accessing mb.com.ph visitors agree to be bound by these terms, If you do not agree to be bound by all of these terms please do not access mb.com.ph.

Visitors agree to use mb.com.ph for lawful purposes only, and in a way that does not infringe the rights of, restrict or inhibit anyone else’s use and enjoyment of mb.com.ph.

This policy does not apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline and/or through other means (for example, via telephone, or through the mail).

Visitors are not allowed to republicise or use any information and photographs including, but not limited to, text, graphics, video, and audio content for commercial purpose except for your own personal use.

* * *

**Legal Disclaimer**

The Company reserves the right to disclose personal data: (i) as required by law, (ii) when the Company believes that disclosure is necessary to protect its rights and interests, or (iii) when the Company is directed to comply with a court order, legal process or judicial proceeding.

* * *

**Use of Cookies**

We use cookies to gather information about mb.com.ph users’ browsing activities so as to improve our services – (i) date/time of your last visit; (ii) which articles that you have commented on; and (iii) what content or comment you have posted on mb.com.ph.

While such cookies are capable of collecting information about which articles on mb.com.ph that you have viewed and the number of these articles, such information will stay on the computer or device that you use to browse mb.com.ph. We will not have records of the same.

We do not use cookies to capture your email address or other personal data about you. You can choose not to accept cookies.

* * *

**Log Files**

The Company gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. These information include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

The Company uses these information to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track movements around the Web Site, and to gather demographic information about the Web Site’s user base as a whole.

The Company uses a third-party tracking service that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to the Web Site in the aggregate, such as page view, number of unique visitors, most visited pages, etc.

* * *

**Links to Other Sites**

This Web Site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by the Company. Please be aware that the Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

The Company encourages visitors to be aware when leaving the Web Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web Site.

* * *

**Security**

The security of personal information is important to the Company, the Company follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to it, both during transmission and at the time the Company receives it. However, no method of transmission over the internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while the Company strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect personal information, the Company cannot guarantee its absolute security.  
Changes in this Privacy Statement

If the Company decides to change its privacy policy, the Company will post those changes to this Privacy Statement on the page and other places it deems appropriate so that visitors are aware of what information the Company collects, how the Company uses it, and under what circumstances, if any, the Company discloses it.

The Company reserves the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time, so please review it frequently.

_**Effective Date: 01 January 2014.**_
